<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
  <jcr:content cq:template="/libs/core/franklin/templates/page" sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/page/v1/page" jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent">
    <root jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/root/v1/root">
      <section sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/section/v1/section" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
        <title sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Adobe Code of Conduct" titleType="h1"/>
        <title_1 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Our Pledge" titleType="h2"/>
        <text sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;In the interest of fostering an open and welcoming environment, we as
                    contributors and maintainers pledge to making participation in our project and
                    our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body
                    size, disability, ethnicity, gender identity and expression, level of experience,
                    nationality, personal appearance, race, religion, or sexual identity and
                    orientation.&lt;/p&gt;"/>
        <title_2 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Our Standards" titleType="h2"/>
        <text_1 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;Examples of behavior that contributes to creating a positive environment
                    include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Using welcoming and inclusive language&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Being respectful of differing viewpoints and experiences&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Gracefully accepting constructive criticism&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Focusing on what is best for the community&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Showing empathy towards other community members&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Examples of unacceptable behavior by participants include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;The use of sexualized language or imagery and unwelcome sexual attention or
                    advances&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Trolling, insulting/derogatory comments, and personal or political attacks&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Public or private harassment&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Publishing others&#x27; private information, such as a physical or electronic
                    address, without explicit permission&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;Other conduct which could reasonably be considered inappropriate in a
                    professional setting&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;/ul&gt;"/>
        <title_3 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Our Responsibilities" titleType="h2"/>
        <text_2 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;Project maintainers are responsible for clarifying the standards of acceptable
                    behavior and are expected to take appropriate and fair corrective action in
                    response to any instances of unacceptable behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Project maintainers have the right and responsibility to remove, edit, or
                    reject comments, commits, code, wiki edits, issues, and other contributions
                    that are not aligned to this Code of Conduct, or to ban temporarily or
                    permanently any contributor for other behaviors that they deem inappropriate,
                    threatening, offensive, or harmful.&lt;/p&gt;"/>
        <title_4 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Scope" titleType="h2"/>
        <text_3 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct applies both within project spaces and in public spaces
                    when an individual is representing the project or its community. Examples of
                    representing a project or community include using an official project e-mail
                    address, posting via an official social media account, or acting as an appointed
                    representative at an online or offline event. Representation of a project may be
                    further defined and clarified by project maintainers.&lt;/p&gt;"/>
        <title_5 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Enforcement" titleType="h2"/>
        <text_4 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;Instances of abusive, harassing, or otherwise unacceptable behavior may be
                    reported by contacting the project team at &lt;a href&#x3D;&quot;mailto:Grp-opensourceoffice@adobe.com&quot;&gt;Grp-opensourceoffice@adobe.com&lt;/a&gt;. All
                    complaints will be reviewed and investigated and will result in a response that
                    is deemed necessary and appropriate to the circumstances. The project team is
                    obligated to maintain confidentiality with regard to the reporter of an incident.
                    Further details of specific enforcement policies may be posted separately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Project maintainers who do not follow or enforce the Code of Conduct in good
                    faith may face temporary or permanent repercussions as determined by other
                    members of the project&#x27;s leadership.&lt;/p&gt;"/>
        <title_6 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/title/v1/title" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" title="Attribution" titleType="h2"/>
        <text_5 sling:resourceType="core/franklin/components/text/v1/text" jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured" text="&lt;p&gt;This Code of Conduct is adapted from the &lt;a href&#x3D;&quot;http://contributor-covenant.org&quot;&gt;Contributor Covenant&lt;/a&gt;, version 1.4,
                    available at &lt;a href&#x3D;&quot;http://contributor-covenant.org/version/1/4/&quot;&gt;http://contributor-covenant.org/version/1/4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;"/>
      </section>
    </root>
  </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>